{
    "subject": "resource/Cottage_to_Let",
    "predicate": "property/music",
    "object": "resource/Charles_Williams_(composer)",
    "human_readable": "The music of Cottage to Let is composed by Charles Williams.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9877166152000427,
            "question": "Is Charles Williams known for composing music for a piece called 'Cottage to Let'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.92386794090271,
            "question": "Find the composer who created the soundtrack for 'Cottage to Let'."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9236343502998352,
            "question": "Who composed the music for 'Cottage to Let'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8119553327560425,
            "question": "What is the name of the composer who created the music for 'Cottage to Let'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7960907220840454,
            "question": "Can you tell me the name of the composer behind the music in 'Cottage to Let'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7908764481544495,
            "question": "Charles Williams is credited with composing what?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7883204221725464,
            "question": "Who composed the music for the theatrical production 'Cottage to Let'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.787778913974762,
            "question": "What musical piece features the compositions of Charles Williams?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7517616152763367,
            "question": "What is Charles Williams known for composing?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5681241750717163,
            "question": "What musical work is associated with Charles Williams?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The music of Cottage to Let is composed by Charles Williams.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3805_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Charles Williams known for composing?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3805_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What musical piece features the compositions of Charles Williams?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3805_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who composed the music for the theatrical production 'Cottage to Let'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3805_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3805_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3805_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3805_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3805_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3805_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3805_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3805_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3805_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3805_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3805_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"The music of Cottage to Let is composed by Charles Williams.\" Specifically, document 23.txt mentions \"music: Charles Williams\" in its description of the film \"Cottage to Let,\" which aligns with the query."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}